<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="" type="text/xsl" ?>
<horoscopes>
  
    <starSign sign="Aries">
      <name>Aries</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			March 21
		</from>
		<to>
			April 19
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>You will be loaded with energy and will do something extraordinary today.
	 Investment made today will enhance your prosperity and financial security.
	 Children could make the day very hard for you.
	 Use affection weapon to keep their interest and avoid any undue stress. Remember love begets love.
	 Love journey sweet but short lived Tact will be required while handling colleagues.
	 Someone from your past is likely to contact you and make it a memorable day. 
	 If your plan of meeting someone got ruined today because of your spouse's health, you will get to spend even a better time together.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
      </starSign>
	  
      <starSign sign="Taurus">
      <name>Taurus</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			April 20
		</from>
		<to>
			May 20
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Sort out your tension for mental peace.
	 Today you can easily raise capital- collect outstanding debts- or ask for funds to work on new projects.
	 Excellent day to plan out things for your progeny. Show your love by placing flower at your window.
	 Keep away from signing any new joint ventures and partnerships.
	 Excellent day for social as well as religious functions. 
	 You keep getting jokes on married life over social media, 
	 but today you will get really emotional when the startling beautiful facts about your married life will come afore you.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Gemini">
      <name>Gemini</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			May 21
		</from>
		<to>
			June 20
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Try to improve your health and overall personality for a better life.
	 Incase you are looking for ways to make little extra money- invest in secure financial schemes.
	 News of family secret may surprise you. All those complaints and grudges in your relationship will
	 vanish on this amazing day. Your competitive nature will help you stay ahead of others.
	 Travel plans if any-might get postponed due to last minute changes in your schedule. 
	 Your marriage will see a wonderful phase during this day.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Cancer">
      <name>Cancer</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			June 21
		</from>
		<to>
			July 22
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>You will sacrifice your happiness for the sake of your family.
	 But it has to be devoid of any interest and expectations. 
	 Travel for some prove hectic and stressful-but financially rewarding.
	 Home-improvement projects should be considered. Don't waste your time in finding fault in your beloved.
	 Good day to start a new venture in partnership. All are likely to be benefited. 
	 But think before joining hands with partners. Unexpected travel for some proves hectic and stressful.
	 If you got angry on your spouse, you will get a quick response. So, stay controlled.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Leo">
      <name>Leo</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			July 23
		</from>
		<to>
			August 22
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>A day of recreation and fun. Monetary gains will be from one than one source.
	 You are most likely to face criticism at home because of your careless behaviour.
	 Physical existence is now of no consideration, as you feel yourself into each other in love all the
	 time. Do not sign any business/legal document without reading between the lines.
	 Volunteering work that you do today will help not only those you assist but will help you look at
	 yourself more positively. Marriages are made in heaven, your spouse will prove this to you today.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Virgo">
      <name>Virgo</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			August 23
		</from>
		<to>
			September 22
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Your rash behaviour may spoil the relationship with wife. 
	 Think the repercussions of your behaviour before doing anything silly.
	 If possible go away to change your mood. Perfect day to purchase items that would grow in value.
	 Make arrangement with your spouse to finish off pending household work. 
	 Wrong communication or a message might make your day dull. 
	 Long ambition to join marketing field may materialize.
	 It will give you tremendous joy and remove all hassles which you had faced during procuring the job.
	 Your ability to act swiftly to problems will bring you recognition.
	 Your spouse might make an issue of something he/she heard in the neighborhood.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Libra">
      <name>Libra</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			September 23
		</from>
		<to>
			October 22
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Creative work will keep you relaxed. Unexpected bills will increase financial burden.
	 Loved ones might be annoyed if you do not spend time with them.
	 You can experience the pain of love. Use your intellectual power to your benefit. 
	 It will help you in completing professional projects and give new ideas. 
	 Rash driving and risk should not be taken while on the road. 
	 Your spouse might come under the adverse influence of others and fight with you, but your love and 
	 compassion will settle everything down.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Scorpio">
      <name>Scorpio</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			October 23
		</from>
		<to>
			November 21
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Keep yourself involved in activities that will help you keep your cool.
	 Financial problems ruin your ability to think constructively.
	 Gift from an overseas relative will make you happy. 
	 New romance seems certain for some- Your love will blossom your life. No matter how much your seniors
	 or colleagues provoke you, just be like Buddha at work today. Good day to visit a lawyer to take some 
	 legal advice. The day is exclusive in your regular married life, you will experience something really
	 unusual today.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Sagittarius">
      <name>Sagittarius</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			November 22
		</from>
		<to>
			December 21
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Work pressure and discord at home might bring some stress.
	 You should look twice at investment schemes that are presented to you today. 
	 Your timely help would save someone's life. 
	 The news would make your family members proud and would also inspire them.
	 Love is limitless, love is boundless; you must have heard these things before.
	 But today, you will experience it. There's little time to rest today-as pending task will keep you 
	 occupied. Some of you will undertake a distant journey-which will be hectic-but highly rewarding.
	 Life is going to be really wonderful today because your spouse has planned something special.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Capricorn">
      <name>Capricorn</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			December 22
		</from>
		<to> 
			January 19
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Avoid overstraining as it would only lead to stress and exhaustion. 
	 Don't overspend too much in order to impress others. You are most likely to make some major changes
	 in and around your house today. Today, you will know that your love partner is the one who will love
	 you till eternity. Opportunities to show your skills will be with you today. Travel will be beneficial
	 but expensive. You will have a series of quarrels that will make you feel like giving up your
	 relationship. However, do not give in that easily.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Aquarius">
      <name>Aquarius</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			January 20
		</from>
		<to>
			February 18
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Spend some time with close friends in order to relax.
	 You will come up with brilliant new ideas that will bring financial gains. 
	 Give priorities to the needs of family members. Involve yourself to share their joy and sorrow to 
	 realize them that you care for them. You will be popular and easily attract members of the opposite sex.
	 Today you will be in the spotlight- and success is well within your reach. 
	 Secondhand news should be verified. You will refresh the old beautiful days of courtship,
	 chasing, and wooing in your married life.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
   
      <starSign sign="Pisces">
      <name>Pisces</name>
     <date>
		<from>
			February 19
		</from>
		<to>
			March 20
		</to>
	 </date>
	 <horoscope>Self medication could cause drug dependency.
	 Take a physician advice before taking any drug-otherwise chances of drug dependency are high.
	 You will like to overspend on others. Proper dialogue and co-operation will improve relationship with
	 spouse. Likely to experience a different kind of romance. Looks like you might cause a big harm to your company today; just be aware. Secondhand news should be verified. 
	 It's a good day to romance with your better half.</horoscope> <!-- INSERT HOROSCOPE HERE -->
   </starSign>
	
</horoscopes>